[{"instructions":"Let's define a new operation +<sub>6</sub>. This operation will give us a way of combining two of the numbers 0, 1, 2, 3, 4, 5 to get another one of them back. To perform +<sub>6</sub>, you start with the first number, and then add the second one to it. If the sum is smaller than 6, that's your result. If the sum is 6 or bigger, you subtract 6 to get your result. (That's why the operation is called +<sub>6</sub>.) <br /><br />For example, 3 +<sub>6</sub> 5 = 2, because 3 + 5 = 8, and 8 is bigger than 6, so we subtract 6, and 8 - 6 = 2. So 3 +<sub>6</sub> 5 = 2.<br /><br />Similarly, 1 +<sub>6</sub> 4 = 5, because 1 + 4 = 5, and 5 is less than 6 so we leave it alone.<br /><br />Click Continue when you're ready to move on.","rt":104701,"trial_type":"instructions","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":1,"time_elapsed":156028,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0"},{"instructions":"Do you see how +<sub>6</sub> works? By subtracting 6 every time we get above 5, we ensure t hat when  we combine two numbers using +<sub>6</sub>, we only produce numbers between 0 and 5.<br /><br />Click Continue when you're ready to move on.","rt":5325,"trial_type":"instructions","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":2,"time_elapsed":161353,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0"},{"question":"Now try one on your own! What is 4 +<sub>6</sub> 5? <br /><br /> (Remember, to perform +<sub>6</sub>, you start with the first number, and then add the second one to it. If the sum is smaller than 6, that's your result. If the sum is 6 or bigger, you subtract 6 to get your result.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"3","response":"3","response_history":["3"],"rt":4831,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":3,"time_elapsed":166185,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.3-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! 4 +<sub>6</sub> 5 = 3 because 4 + 5 = 9 and 9 - 6 = 3.","rt":2495,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":4,"time_elapsed":168681,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.3-0"},{"question":"What is 3 +<sub>6</sub> 2? <br /><br /> (Remember, to perform +<sub>6</sub>, you start with the first number, and then add the second one to it. If the sum is smaller than 6, that's your result. If the sum is 6 or bigger, you subtract 6 to get your result.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"5","response":"5","response_history":["5"],"rt":3601,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":5,"time_elapsed":172282,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.3-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! 3 +<sub>6</sub> 2 = 5 because 3 + 2 = 5 and 5 is less than 6.","rt":1227,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":6,"time_elapsed":173510,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.3-0"},{"question":"What is 1 +<sub>6</sub> 5? <br /><br /> (Remember, to perform +<sub>6</sub>, you start with the first number, and then add the second one to it. If the sum is smaller than 6, that's your result. If the sum is 6 or bigger, you subtract 6 to get your  result. )","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"0","response":"0","response_history":["0"],"rt":3553,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":7,"time_elapsed":177065,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.3-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! 1 +<sub>6</sub> 5 = 0 because 1 + 5 = 6 and 6 - 6 = 0.","rt":1203,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":8,"time_elapsed":178268,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.3-0"},{"question":"What is 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1? <br /><br /> (Remember, to perform +<sub>6</sub>, you start with the first number, and then add the second one to it. If the sum is smaller than 6, that's your result. If the sum is 6 or bigger, you subtract 6 to get your result.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"2","response":"2","response_history":["2"],"rt":2635,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":9,"time_elapsed":180904,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.3-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1 =  2 becaus e 1 + 1 = 2 and 2 is less than 6.","rt":1076,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":10,"time_elapsed":181980,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.3-0"},{"question":"What is 3 +<sub>6</sub> 0? <br /><br /> (Remember, to perform +<sub>6</sub>, you start with the first number, and then add the second one to it. If the sum is smaller than 6, that's your result. If the sum is 6 or bigger, you subtract 6 to get your result.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"3","response":"3","response_history":["3"],"rt":5146,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":11,"time_elapsed":187126,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.3-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! 3 +<sub>6</sub> 0 = 3 because 3 + 0 = 3 and 3 is less than 6.","rt":1132,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":12,"time_elapsed":188258,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.3-0"},{"question":"What is 4 +<sub>6</sub> 4? <br /><br /> (Remember, to perform +<sub>6</sub>, you start with the  first n umber, and then add the second one to it. If the sum is smaller than 6, that's your result. If the sum is 6 or bigger, you subtract 6 to get your result.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"2","response":"2","response_history":["2"],"rt":2683,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":13,"time_elapsed":190942,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.3-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! 4 +<sub>6</sub> 4 = 2 because 4 + 4 = 8 and 8 - 6 = 2.","rt":1148,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":14,"time_elapsed":192090,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.3-0"},{"question":"What is 1 +<sub>6</sub> 3? <br /><br /> (Remember, to perform +<sub>6</sub>, you start with the first number, and then add the second one to it. If the sum is smaller than 6, that's your result. If the sum is 6 or bigger, you subtract 6 to get your result.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"4","response":"4","response_history":["4"],"rt":2928,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":15,"time_elapsed":195018,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.3-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! 1 +<sub>6</sub> 3 = 4 because 1 + 3 = 4 and 4 is less than 6.","rt":1216,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":16,"time_elapsed":196234,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.3-0"},{"question":"What is 4 +<sub>6</sub> 3? <br /><br /> (Remember, to perform +<sub>6</sub>, you start with the first number, and then add the second one to it. If the sum is smaller than 6, that's your result. If the sum is 6 or bigger, you subtract 6 to get your result.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"1","response":"1","response_history":["1"],"rt":2182,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":17,"time_elapsed":198416,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.3-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! 4 +<sub>6</sub> 3 = 1 because 4 + 3 = 7 and 7 - 6 = 1.","rt":2018,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":18,"time_elapsed":200434,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.3-0"},{"question":"What is 0 +<sub>6</sub> 5? <br /><br /> (Remember, to perform +<sub>6</sub>, you start with the first number, and then add the second one to it. If the sum is smaller than 6, that's your result. If the sum is 6 or bigger, you subtract 6 to get your result.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"5","response":"5","response_history":["5"],"rt":2085,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":19,"time_elapsed":202519,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.3-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! 0 +<sub>6</sub> 5 = 5 because 0 + 5 = 5 and 5 is less than 6.","rt":865,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":20,"time_elapsed":203385,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.3-0"},{"question":"What is 2 +<sub>6</sub> 5? <br /><br /> (Remember, to perform +<sub>6</sub>, you start with the first number, and then add the second one to it. If the sum is smaller than 6, that's your result. If the sum is 6 or bigger, you  subtrac t 6 to get your result.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"1","response":"1","response_history":["1"],"rt":1937,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":21,"time_elapsed":205323,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.3-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! 2 +<sub>6</sub> 5 = 1 because 2 + 5 = 7 and 7 - 6 = 1.","rt":1837,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":22,"time_elapsed":207161,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.3-0"},{"instructions":"Now we're going to discuss a couple special properties of this new operation, +<sub>6</sub> that we've learned. First, notice that the number 0 behaves in a special way under +<sub>6</sub>. Whenever we combine 0 with anything else, we get that same thing back. We'll say that 0 is the <i>identity</i> under +<sub>6</sub>, because when you combine it with something it gives you that identical thing back.","rt":7804,"trial_type":"instructions","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":23,"time_elapsed":214967,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0"},{"instructions":"Now that we know 0 is the identity under +<sub>6</sub>, we're going to make a new definition. We'll say that the <i>inverse</i> of a number is the element that you combine with it to produce the identity. For example, 5 +<sub>6</sub> 1 = 0, so we say 1 is the inverse of 5 under +<sub>6</sub>, (remember 0 is the identity under +<sub>6</sub>). Similarly, 3 is its own inverse under +<sub>6</sub>, because 3 +<sub>6</sub> 3 = 0.","rt":22272,"trial_type":"instructions","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":24,"time_elapsed":237240,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0"},{"question":"Now you try! What is the inverse of 4 under +<sub>6</sub>? <br /><br /> (Remember, the inverse of an element is the thing which you combine with it to produce the identity.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"2","response":"2","response_history":["2"],"rt":3353,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":25,"time_elapsed":240594,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.7-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! The inverse of 4 under +<sub>6</sub> is 2 because 4 +<sub>6</sub> 2 = 0, and 0 is the identity under +<sub>6</sub>.","rt":1399,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":26,"time_elapsed":241994,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.7-0"},{"question":"What is the inverse of 1 under +<sub>6</sub>? <br /><br /> (Remember, the inverse of an element is the thing which you combine with it to produce the identity.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"5","response":"5","response_history":["5"],"rt":2525,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":27,"time_elapsed":244520,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.7-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! The inverse of 1 under +<sub>6</sub> is 5 because 1 +<sub>6</sub> 5 = 0, and 0 is the identity under +<sub>6</sub>.","rt":1479,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":28,"time_elapsed":246000,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.7-0"},{"question":"What is the inv erse of  3 under +<sub>6</sub>? <br /><br /> (Remember, the inverse of an element is the thing which you combine with it to produce the identity.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"3","response":"3","response_history":["3"],"rt":2245,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":29,"time_elapsed":248246,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.7-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! The inverse of 3 under +<sub>6</sub> is 3 because 3 +<sub>6</sub> 3 = 0, and 0 is the identity under +<sub>6</sub>.","rt":951,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":30,"time_elapsed":249198,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.7-0"},{"question":"What is the inverse of 2 under +<sub>6</sub>? <br /><br /> (Remember, the inverse of an element is the thing which you combine with it to produce the identity.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"4","response":"4","response_history":["4"],"rt":2006,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":31,"time_elapsed":251204,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.7-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! The inverse of 2 under +<sub>6</sub> is 4 because 2 +<sub>6</sub> 4 = 0, and 0 is the identity under +<sub>6</sub>.","rt":1363,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":32,"time_elapsed":252568,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.7-0"},{"question":"What is the inverse of 0 under +<sub>6</sub>? <br /><br /> (Remember, the inverse of an element is the thing which you combine with it to produce the identity.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"0","response":"0","response_history":["6","0"],"rt":12404,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":33,"time_elapsed":264973,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.7-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! The inverse of 0 under +<sub>6</sub> is 0 because 0 +<sub>6</sub> 0 = 0, and 0 is the identity under +<sub>6</sub>.","rt":1259,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":34,"time_elapsed":266233,"internal_chunk_id":" 0-0.7-0"},{"instructions":"It is also possible to successively apply +<sub>6</sub>, and the operation can simply be performed starting with the left-most pair. For example, 2 +<sub>6</sub> 3 +<sub>6</sub> 4 = 5 +<sub>6</sub> 4 = 3.","rt":18750,"trial_type":"instructions","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":35,"time_elapsed":284984,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0"},{"instructions":"We have one last definition to learn today, using the successive operations we just learned. Let's start with an example. Under our operation +<sub>6</sub> we can make every other number using just 1: 2 = 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1, 3 = 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1, 4 = 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1, 5 = 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1, and 0 = 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1. Because 1 can make every other element under +<sub>6</sub>, we say that 1 is a <i>generator</i> under +<sub>6</sub>. <br /><br /> However,  2 is not  a generator under +<sub>6</sub>, because 4 = 2 +<sub>6</sub> 2, and 0 = 2 +<sub>6</sub> 2 +<sub>6</sub> 2, but there is no way to make 1, 3, or 5 using just 2.","rt":43672,"trial_type":"instructions","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":36,"time_elapsed":328657,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0"},{"question":"Now you try! Is 3 a generator under +<sub>6</sub>? <br /><br /> (Remember, a generator is an element which can make every other element.)","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["Yes","No"],"correct_response":"No","response":"No","response_history":["No"],"rt":3887,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":37,"time_elapsed":332545,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.10-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! 3 is not a generator under +<sub>6</sub>, because 3 = 3, 0 = 3 +<sub>6</sub> 3, but there is no way to make 1, 2, 4, or 5 using just 3.","rt":1170,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":38,"time_elapsed":333717,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.10-0"},{"question":"Is 5  a generator under +<sub>6</sub>? <br /><br /> (Remember, a generator is an element which can make every other element.)","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["Yes","No"],"correct_response":"Yes","response":"No","response_history":["No"],"rt":1764,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":39,"time_elapsed":335481,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.10-0"},{"feedback":"Sorry, that's incorrect. 5 is a generator under +<sub>6</sub>, because 5 = 5, 4 = 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5, 3 = 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5, 2 = 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5, 1 = 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5, and 0 = 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5, so you can make all of the numbers under +<sub>6</sub> using 5","rt":4778,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":40,"time_elapsed":340259,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.10-0"},{"question":"Is 4 a generator under +<sub>6</sub>? <br  /><br />  (Remember, a generator is an element which can make every other element.)","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["Yes","No"],"correct_response":"No","response":"Yes","response_history":["Yes"],"rt":8513,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":41,"time_elapsed":348772,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.10-0"},{"feedback":"Sorry, that's incorrect. 4 is not a generator under +<sub>6</sub>, because 4 = 4, 2 = 4 +<sub>6</sub> 4, and 0 = 4 +<sub>6</sub> 4 +<sub>6</sub> 4, but there is no way to make 1, 3, or 5 using just 4.","rt":1075,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":42,"time_elapsed":349848,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.10-0"},{"question":"Is 0 a generator under +<sub>6</sub>? <br /><br /> (Remember, a generator is an element which can make every other element.)","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["Yes","No"],"correct_response":"No","response":"No","response_history":["No"],"rt":2461,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":43,"time_elapsed":352310,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.10-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! 0 is not a generator under +<sub>6</sub>, because 0 = 0, but there is no way to make 1, 2, 3, 4, or 5 using just 0.","rt":1175,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":44,"time_elapsed":353486,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.10-0"},{"instructions":"Now we are going to ask you some questions about a new operation, +<sub>9</sub>, on the numbers 0, 1, 2, 3, 4, 5, 6, 7, 8. It works exactly like +<sub>6</sub>, except now after adding the two numbers you subtract 9 if your result is 9 or greater. <br /><br />Do you see how +<sub>9</sub> works just like +<sub>6</sub>? By subtracting 9 every time we get above 8, we ensure that when we combine two numbers using +<sub>9</sub>, we only produce numbers between 0 and 8.<br /><br />We'll give you one practice question with feedback to make sure you understand the new operation. After that, try to complete the remaining questions as accurately  as poss ible.","rt":10505,"trial_type":"instructions","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":45,"time_elapsed":363992,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0"},{"question":"Practice: What is 5 +<sub>9</sub> 5?","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"1","response":"1","response_history":["1"],"rt":3019,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":46,"time_elapsed":367012,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.12-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! 5 +<sub>9</sub> 5 = 1 because 5 + 5 = 10 and 10 - 9 = 1.","rt":1283,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":47,"time_elapsed":368296,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.12-0"},{"question":"What is 3 +<sub>9</sub> 3?","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"6","response":"6","response_history":["6"],"rt":3224,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":48,"time_elapsed":371520,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.12-0"},{"question":"What is 7 +<sub>9</sub> 4?","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"2","response":"2","response_history":["2"],"rt":2243,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":49,"time_elapsed":373764,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.12-0"},{"question":"What is 1 +<sub>9</sub> 8?","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"0","response":"0","response_history":["0"],"rt":2771,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":50,"time_elapsed":376536,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.12-0"},{"question":"What is 5 +<sub>9</sub> 4?","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"0","response":"0","response_history":["0"],"rt":4562,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":51,"time_elapsed":381098,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.12-0"},{"question":"What is 6 +<sub>9</sub> 6?","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"3","response":"3","response_history":["3"],"rt":5065,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":52,"time_elapsed":386163,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.12-0"},{"question":"What is 4 +<sub>9</sub> 1? Please explain in words how you got your answer.","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"","response":"four plus one is five, which is less than 9 so the answer is 5","response_history":["5, 4+1","5, 4+","5, 4","5, four plus 1four ","four plus one is five, which is less than 9 so the answer is 5"],"rt":29434,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":53,"time_elapsed":415598,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.12-0"},{"question":"What is 8 +<sub>9</sub> 4? Please explain in words how you got your answer.","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"","response":"eight plus four is 12 which is greater than 9. subtract 9 from 12 and the answer is three.","response_history":["3","eight plus 4 is 12","eight plus 4 is 1","eight plus 4 is ","eight plus 4 is","eight plus 4 i","eight plus 4 ","eight plus 4","eight plus four is 12 a","eight plus four is 12 which is great er than  9. subtract 9 and the ","eight plus four is 12 which is greater than 9. subtract 9 and the","eight plus four is 12 which is greater than 9. subtract 9 and th","eight plus four is 12 which is greater than 9. subtract 9 and t","eight plus four is 12 which is greater than 9. subtract 9 and ","eight plus four is 12 which is greater than 9. subtract 9 and","eight plus four is 12 which is greater than 9. subtract 9 an","eight plus four is 12 which is greater than 9. subtract 9 a","eight plus four is 12 which is greater than 9. subtract 9 from 12 and the as","eight plus four is 12 which is greater than 9. subtract 9 from 12 and the answer is 3","eight plus four is 12 which is greater than 9. subtract 9 from 12 and the answer is three."],"rt":30060,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":54,"time_elapsed":445659,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.12-0"},{"question":"What is the identity under +<sub>9</sub>? Please explain in words how you got your answer.","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"0","response":"anything less than nine remains, anything greater than nine has nine subtracted. 0-8 are acceptable results.","response_history":["anything under ","anything under","anything unde","anything und","anything un","anything u","anything less than nine remains, anything greater than nine has nine subtracted. 0-8 are acceptable results."],"rt":52260,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":55,"time_elapsed":497920,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.12-0"},{"question":"What is the inverse of 5 under +<sub>9</sub>?","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"4","response":"5","response_history":["5"],"rt":6475,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":56,"time_elapsed":504396,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.12-0"},{"question":"What is the inverse of 2 under +<sub>9</sub>?","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"7","response":"8","response_history":["8"],"rt":4423,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":57,"time_elapsed":508820,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.12-0"},{"question":"What is the inverse of 0 under +<sub>9</sub>?","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"0","response":"0","response_history":["0"],"rt":2329,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":58,"time_elapsed":511150,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.12-0"},{"question":"What is the inverse of 3 under +<sub>9</sub>? Please explain in words how you got your answer.","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"","response":"the answer is 7. which is the same difference from 9 and zero is from three","response_history":["7 the ","7 the","7 th","7 t","7 ","7","the answer is 7. the an","the answer is 7. the a","the answer is 7. the ","the answer is 7. the","the answer is 7. th","the answer is 7. t","the answer is 7. the in","the answer is 7. the i","the answer is 7. the ","the answer is 7. the","the answer is  7. th","the answer is 7. t","the answer is 7. 9 ","the answer is 7. 9","the answer is 7. which is the same difference from zero as 3","the answer is 7. which is the same difference from zero as ","the answer is 7. which is the same difference from zero as","the answer is 7. which is the same difference from zero a","the answer is 7. which is the same difference from zero ","the answer is 7. which is the same difference from zero","the answer is 7. which is the same difference from zer","the answer is 7. which is the same difference from ze","the answer is 7. which is the same difference from z","the answer is 7. which is the same difference from 9 and zero is from three"],"rt":56494,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":59,"time_elapsed":567644,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.12-0"},{"question":"Is 2 a generator under +<sub>9</sub>? Please explain in words how you got your answer.","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"","response":"I'm no t sure.  I don't understand generators very well in this lesson.","response_history":["I'm not sure. I don't understand generators very well in this lesso.","I'm not sure. I don't understand generators very well in this lesson."],"rt":21793,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":60,"time_elapsed":589438,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.12-0"},{"question":"Is 3 a generator under +<sub>9</sub>? Please explain in words how you got your answer.","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"","response":"I'm not sure. I don't understand generators very well in this lesson. I don't think so.","response_history":["I'm not sure. I don't understand generators very well in this lesson. I don't think so."],"rt":8573,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":61,"time_elapsed":598011,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.12-0"},{"question":"Is 5 a generator under +<sub>9</sub>? Please explain in words how you got your answer.","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"","response":"No.","response_history":["No."],"rt":3696,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":62,"time_elapsed":601707,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.12-0"},{"question":"Is 6 a generator under +<sub>9</sub>? Please explain in words how you got your answer.","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"","response":"No? I'm not sure. I don't understand generators very well in this lesson.","response_history":["no.","no","n","No? I'm not sure. I don't understand generators very well in this lesson."],"rt":7122,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":63,"time_elapsed":608829,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.12-0"},{"instructions":"Now we'd like to ask you some questions about +<sub>n</sub>, where n could be any postive counting number. For example, n could be 3, or n could be any other counting number you can think of. If you need to write the operation, you can use +_n, and your answers can includ e n to s tand in for the arbitrary value if necessary.","rt":53285,"trial_type":"instructions","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":64,"time_elapsed":662114,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0"},{"question":"What is the formula for the inverse of 1 under +<sub>n</sub>?","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"n-1","response":"1+_n","response_history":["1-","1","1+n","1+_n"],"rt":76303,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":65,"time_elapsed":738418,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.14-0"},{"question":"What is the formula for the inverse of an element x under +<sub>n</sub>? Please explain in words how you got your answer.","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"n-x","response":"You have not provided enough information to do this. ","response_history":["You have not prob","You have not provided engouh","You have not provided engou","You have not provided engo","You have not provided eng","You have not provided enough e","You have not  provided  enough infomration ","You have not provided enough infomration","You have not provided enough infomratio","You have not provided enough infomrati","You have not provided enough infomrat","You have not provided enough infomra","You have not provided enough infomr","You have not provided enough infom","You have not provided enough information to do this. "],"rt":59027,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":66,"time_elapsed":797446,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.14-0"},{"question":"Is there a pattern to which elements are generators? How can you know if an element x is a generator under +<sub>n</sub> without seeing whether it can make all the elements?.","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"","response":"I'm sure that there is a pattern but I don't understand what it is. I'd probably have to just add each number together to see.","response_history":["I'm sure ther","I'm sure the","I'm sure that h","I'm sure that there is a pattern bu t I don' t understand what it is. I'd probably b","I'm sure that there is a pattern but I don't understand what it is. I'd probably have to just add them","I'm sure that there is a pattern but I don't understand what it is. I'd probably have to just add the","I'm sure that there is a pattern but I don't understand what it is. I'd probably have to just add th","I'm sure that there is a pattern but I don't understand what it is. I'd probably have to just add t","I'm sure that there is a pattern but I don't understand what it is. I'd probably have to just add each number together to see."],"rt":28370,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":67,"time_elapsed":825817,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.14-0"},{"question":"True or false: If x is an odd number, it must be a generator under +<sub>n</sub>.","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["True","False"],"correct_response":"False","response":"True","response_history":["True"],"rt":7235,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":68,"time_elapsed":833053,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.14-0"},{"question":"True or false: If x is an even number, it must not be a generator under +<sub>n</sub>.","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["True","False"],"correct_response":"False","response":"True","response_history":["True"],"rt":4311,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":69,"time_elapsed":837365,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.14-0"},{"question":"True or false: If x is not a generator under +<sub>n</sub>, x must be a divisor of n, that is, x must divide n evenly, with no remainder.","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["True","False"],"correct_response":"False","response":"True","response_history":["True"],"rt":14816,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":70,"time_elapsed":852181,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.14-0"},{"question":"True or false: If x is not a generator under +<sub>n</sub>, x must be a multiple of a divisor of n. Please explain in words wh y your a nswer is correct.","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"True","response":"Literally no idea what this is asking. I don't know if this is true or false so I don't know why its correct.","response_history":["It","I","Literally no idea what this is aske","Literally no idea what this is asking ","Literally no idea what this is asking. I don't know if this is true or false so I od","Literally no idea what this is asking. I don't know if this is true or false so I o","Literally no idea what this is asking. I don't know if this is true or false so I don't knkw","Literally no idea what this is asking. I don't know if this is true or false so I don't knk","Literally no idea what this is asking. I don't know if this is true or false so I don't know what ","Literally no idea what this is asking. I don't know if this is true or false so I don't know what","Literally no idea what this is asking. I don't know if this is true or false so I don't know wha","Liter ally no  idea what this is asking. I don't know if this is true or false so I don't know wh","Literally no idea what this is asking. I don't know if this is true or false so I don't know w","Literally no idea what this is asking. I don't know if this is true or false so I don't know if","Literally no idea what this is asking. I don't know if this is true or false so I don't know i","Literally no idea what this is asking. I don't know if this is true or false so I don't know why its correct."],"rt":50000,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":71,"time_elapsed":902181,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.14-0"},{"question":"If an element x is a generator under +<sub>n</sub>, is its inverse a generator under +<sub>n</sub> always, sometimes, or never?","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["Always","Sometimes","Never"],"correct_response":"Always","response":"Always","response_history":["Sometimes","Always"],"rt":31904,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":72,"time_elapsed":934086,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.14-0"},{"question":"if an element x is a generator under +<sub>n</sub>, is x +<sub>n</sub> x a generator under +<sub>n</sub> always, sometimes, or never? Please explain in words why your answer is correct.","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"sometimes","response":"I haven't taken a math class in almost 15 years. You haven't explained this concept!","response_history":["I haven't taken a math class in almost 15 years. You haven't a","I haven't taken a math class in almost 15 years. You haven't exla","I haven't taken a math class in almost 15 years. You haven't exl","I haven't taken a math class in almost 15 years. You haven't explain ","I haven't taken a math class in almost 15 years. You haven't explained this concept ","I haven't taken a math class in almost 15 years. You haven't explained this concept!"],"rt":36638,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":73,"time_elapsed":970725,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.14-0"},{"question":"If an element x is not a generator under +<sub>n</sub>, is x +<sub>n</sub> x a generator under +<sub>n</sub> always, sometimes, or never?","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["Always","Sometimes","Never"],"correct_response":"Never","response":"Never","response_history":["Sometimes","Never"],"rt":14499,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":74,"time_elapsed":985225,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.14-0"},{"instructions":"We would like to ask you some questions about your background. Please press Continue to continue.","rt":1399,"trial_type":"instructions","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":75,"time_elapsed":986625,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.15-0"},{"question":"What is your age?","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"","response":"32","response_history":["32"],"rt":1926,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":76,"time_elapsed":988551,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.15-0 "},{"question":"What is your level of education?","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["Did not graduate high school","High school diploma","Some college, no degree","Associates Degree","Bachelors Degree","Some graduate school, no degree","Masters Degree","Doctorate, M.D., etc."],"correct_response":"","response":"Bachelors Degree","response_history":["Bachelors Degree"],"rt":3558,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":77,"time_elapsed":992109,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.15-0"},{"question":"What is the most advanced math class you've completed? If you have multiple classes and you're not sure which one is most advanced, please list them.","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"","response":"College Algebra","response_history":["College Alebra","College Alebr","College Aleb","College Ale","College Algebra"],"rt":7515,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":78,"time_elapsed":999624,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.15-0"},{"question":"How familiar are you with the concept of modular arithmetic?","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["1 - never heard of it","2 - heard of it but didn't know what it was","3 - seen it used or explained","4 - used it but not often or recently","5 - used it, remember and understand it"],"correct_response":"1","response":"1 - never heard of it","response_history":["1 - never heard of it"],"rt":4128,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":79,"time_elapsed":1003753,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.15-0"},{"question":"How familiar are you with the concept of a mathematical group?","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["1 - never heard of it","2 - heard of it but didn't know what it was","3 - seen it used or explained","4 - used it but not often or recently","5 - used it, remember and understand it"],"correct_response":"1","response":"1 - never heard of it","response_history":["1 - never heard of it"],"rt":4143,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":80,"time_elapsed":1007896,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.15-0"},{"question":"Do you feel you learned something from this HIT?","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["1 - not at all","2 - somewhat","3 - definitely"],"correct_response":"1","response":"2 - somewhat","response_history":["2 - somewhat"],"rt":4243,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":81,"time_elapsed":1012140,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.15-0"},{"question":"Do you feel you understood the concepts in this HIT?","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["1 - not at all","2 - somewhat","3 - definitely"],"correct_response":"1","response":"1 - not at all","response_history":["1 - not at all"],"rt":2417,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":82,"time_elapsed":1014558,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.15-0"},{"question":"Did you enjoy this HIT?","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["1 - not at all","2 - somewhat","3 - definitely"],"correct_response":"1","response":"2 -  somewha t","response_history":["2 - somewhat"],"rt":2591,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":83,"time_elapsed":1017150,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.15-0"},{"question":"What is your gender?","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["Female","Male","Other"],"correct_response":"","response":"Female","response_history":["Female"],"rt":1674,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":84,"time_elapsed":1018824,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.15-0"},{"question":"What is/are your native language(s)? (The languages spoken in your household when you were a child.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"","response":"English","response_history":["English"],"rt":2984,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":85,"time_elapsed":1021808,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.15-0"},{"question":"Did you use pen and paper at any point on this HIT?","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"","response":"No","response_history":["No"],"rt":2836,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":86,"time_elapsed":1024644,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.15-0"},{"question":"Do you have any comments on this HIT?","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"","response":"I hope I am not rejected for not understanding the concepts.","response_history":["I don't u","I don't ","I don't","I don'","I don","I do","I d","I hope I am not rejected for not understanding the concepts."],"rt":12774,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":87,"time_elapsed":1037419,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.15-0"}]